Sure.  The guys give Kunali his first drive today.
So brother, I personally
like this car very much.
Leave it, if you buy that car which has a
screen in the front then I will come to
you everywhere.
What happened?
Oye I went million.
Hey hey what happened?
Leave it, friend, take this car.  It's all a
game.
Brother, the vlog is going well.
Oh, the engine sound is also coming from this.
Hey guys good morning.  Welcome to my new
vlog.  So brother, this time I am going to gift a
new car to Avantika on her birthday.
And this time I want to buy an
electric car because we have a G
Wagon, so brother, I am very happy with an
electric car, so whatever I buy now, I am
thinking of buying an electric car and
gifting it to someone, but I am not able to understand
which car should I gift, there is still time for
his birthday, till then let's decide
properly, today I have ordered
two EV cars from Mahindra, both EV cars have been ordered, let's take a
test drive of both, let's see
which one you like, rest you
also tell in the comments which electric car will be
best for us for daily use
because Avantika goes to many places, on
shoots, on her own and many other things for the
family, so which car will be best
electric, but because the charger is
installed, we can drive it comfortably after charging, the
range should be good, the features should be
good, it is fun to drive, we are looking for such a car, so let's
see
how the Mahindra one looks, today I have ordered two
and guys, I am thinking of reducing the number of cars a bit, I am
thinking of buying a Posh from my garage, it remains
parked, I am
thinking of taking this one out here and  I am also thinking of GLC,
I am thinking that now it is
right to be a little practical, after marriage I have already become old,
anyway I have kept limited cars,
but keep them properly, brother I am most
satisfied with GLC, that is the best,
rest this one does not run at all, Sahil's
jeep is great, if I get an Avantika also then it will be
fine, rest Fortuner is the best
brother
because guys, there is no problem in keeping too many cars, do you
know what insurance is
brother, the insurance of the cars is so expensive, the insurance of the cars, the
insurance of GLC means
more than 10 lakhs are spent every year on the insurance
of the cars, which brother, for the amount of money
you can buy one car, when you have to pay the
insurance of all the cars, then it
seems that so much
money is going into insurance every year, so I am
thinking that by being a little
practical, we have saved that money somewhere else,
in education etc. What is there in that, what are you
saying
brother, Kunali has also come,
you are talking of selling the car, let
me
leave it, friend, I have not even grown up yet
when I  When I turn 18, I will
drive all your cars once and then
you can sell as many cars as you want
but don't send me now friend please
send me when I turn 18
which one do I want to drive I haven't
driven even one yet friend sorry please friend please
don't send me friend
tell me which one do you want to drive it is
strange to me
you want to drive a car
yes
sure yes let me
drive it today it will be
fun guys he will drive the car come let's do
one thing let's make Kunalu drive the car today.
Yes.  Today I have ordered a car which you
can drive.   It
is small.   Are
?   It is
not small but big.   It
is big.
Yes.   It
is very big.
Yes.  You can drive it.
And do you know how?  You can operate it with a remote control.
Big car with remote control.
Really?
No, the guys are lying.
Oh really guys.
Guys, he will bring the smaller car.
No, I am very sure.  Guys let's make Kunali
drive the car for the first time today.  That too with the remote.
Guys, I can't drive a real car.
Otherwise they'll give the toy one to me [sound of clearing throat].  It's
not the toy one,
right?   It must be the
toy one.   It will be
real.   The
elder one doesn't come.  Guys, how much have I seen?  The
big remote control does not come.   It
comes.   It does
n't come.  I am calling.  I am not
coming.  I am telling you, right?   If you get it done
then tell me.
Ok.   Sure, right
?
Yes.
So finally the car has come out which I
am going to drive for Kunal today.  And
we're about to take a test drive.  Let's see how it
looks.  And Kunali still can't believe it.   Do
you still think it's a prank?
And what a prank it is.   Come on.
Guys, the car B6 has already arrived,
we had taken its test drive earlier also.  Let's try it again today
and also let Avantiya try it.
So let's sit inside it.
Brother, the look from outside is very strong.  Meaning it
looks very strong.  Look, let's go inside.  Let's take a
test drive.  Walk well.   I will
drive it first, right?  O Kunali
sat inside first.
And brother, the feeling you get as soon as you sit inside is like you are
sitting in some futuristic car.  Look, this is a
very next level gear.
It looks so cool and its key is
also very switchable,
show it,
see this and there is also a place to keep the key, the key
is there, it is
proper, you can keep the key here like this
and here its modes are parking, reverse,
neutral, drive and look at this, the
gears change in this way, now you see,
you are buying a new car
for me, what else,
really, anything, let it be
friend,
and look at its sunroof, you can drive
that car, you know, and look at its steering
also, it is very unique,
sporty, it is written 'E' here also.
All the controls etc. are here.
And look, there
is not much space here either.  It doesn't seem very open
here either.
So brother, I personally like this car very much.
And there is also a higher level model
which also has a screen.  She is
also a little older.
Screen
Yes Yes
Can Watch TV.
Yes, you can watch TV also.
Yes, take that friend, you will enjoy it a bit.
Yes, Kunal will just sit here and watch TV.
Brother, you will vomit after seeing the burning TV.   Nothing happens.
So I have ordered that one.  I
will take a test drive of that one too.  Let's take this for now.
Then we will take the other one also.  Look wise
I like this one more.  It has more features inside.
If you buy that car which has a
screen in the front, I will come everywhere
with you.
Sure?
So what?
Because you will get to watch TV [nasal sound] in
that.
Sure?
Yes.
Look what brother Kunal is saying.  It doesn't
go anywhere.  If you take that car, I will
come.  It will have a screen to play YouTube.   The
best thing I found was the key feature.
Because we keep the keys here and there.  If it gets
lost then just keep it in its place and it will never get lost
and right now the charging is 64% and the range is showing
301 km.  That's right brother.   The
range is also good.   The
range is also good brother.   You
can come to Delhi right now by sitting in this.   Let's try it
now.  Now you drive.   I have
driven it.  I
like it, friend.
Kunal will definitely manage it, right?
Yes, yes, I will manage.  Guys, here comes another car
which Kunal will like.
Guys, look, I have the key in my hand.
Who knows, you are not coming because I am standing there.
No, she will not come.   It is
coming.  It is coming.  It is coming.
She will come and stop.
Wow, it stopped on its own.
[nasal sound]
Look, I'm pushing the car.
So if you are taking it out from a parking lot,
this is the best feature for that.  Press this button.
Keep it pressed.  That car will come next.
So brother, finally Kunal is going to drive the car.   Should I
press it?
Press, press.
Look brother, Kunal also drove the car today.
Brother,
that too with the remote.
Dude, it's quite good at driving.  So you
will drive this, I will test whether
I stop in the air or not.   There
is so much space here brother.
I can keep my camera here.  Guys, there
is so much space here.  I put away my entire camera.
And look how well I am able to record.
And all the people are coming
into the frame, right?
Yes.
Brother, this is a very nice car.   I
should take this brother.  Guys,
big luxury cars
don't have this feature where I can keep my camera in them.
So let's try the second one now.   The
second one has more features guys.
And she is a little older too.  And
there is a screen for Kunal too.  Guys, let's take a
test drive of the XV9.  Look at this,
Kunal is sitting in the front row.
Why are you sitting in the front row?   The
screen is so big that I thought it had become
small.  If it is this small then it
is so big even here.   I hope
you will enjoy watching this.
Quickly
which
brother, there is a lot of space in the back.
Kunal is asking if games are played in it.
I will start and a nice sound will come.
Okay, see.
Oh brother,
this is even smoother to drive than that.
Guys look at this, there is YouTube also.  Amazon
Prime Jio Hotstar, it has everything brother,
look there are games, you
can download games too,
maybe
one play
travel kar in it,
what happened to you,
oh I am a million, oh
what happened,
friend, buy this car, it has all the games,
sir,
I can't play any game on my iPad, like the ones
on PC, I
can play PC games on the car, friend, buy this
car, please friend, friend, look what all is there
in it, look there is Macallion, there is Batman,
Lagos too, brother, look,
all these games will run on it,
what do I have to buy, just
look at what all is there, this Need for Speed,
look at what amazing games are there,
brother, this will become a gaming car,
and we can also watch our vlogs in it while
driving,
and guys, look at this too, it has a full moon roof
till the back and white seats, so this also
looks very cool, friend [Music] I will get
everything planned tomorrow in offroading,
brother, the vlog is going well,
oh, the engine sound is also coming in it.
So brother, I like
this car very much.  Now it seems better to
me because it is a screen, so we
can watch anything on it and play games.  I
can do anything brother.
Friend, I have seen this car for the first time.   It has everything from
TV to games.
Everyone can see the vlog.
Sorry friend, take this car friend.  In this I can
see all these cartoons.  I can also play games.
Excellent.
So if I buy this car, you will travel everywhere.
And will I go everywhere?
Definitely everywhere.   What else
?   What
if it doesn't work?  what will I go I
promise 100% 100%
101% friend you buy a
good car we have to buy
this car for the city which one did you like out of the two friend
this one I do
n't understand
friend understand
Kunali which one did you like out of the two
this one in this one is the one with
controls
which one
in this one
no the one with forward and reverse
yes this one also has it I
mean it has more features in it but I
like the look of this one first tell me for sure you will get it for you right
you are definitely buying it
oh I will get it for sure I will not do it
like Minir you didn't do it like Mini I even
brought it after showing it off no no I will not take it for sure I do
n't know for sure do it like that one right now
you decide which one to buy right now
friend
take this one what is there in it to keep the camera so
you have a little hands God has given
you hands keep it in your hands why do you have to keep the camera in the car
what is the difference in the price ok there is a
difference of 4 lakhs I just like this one I
also like it because it is for
vlogging
but it has
features so we will put everything in that one  If we give it
in the same car then how will it
sell?
Hey friend guys, I really like the black one
because I can keep a camera there, it's cool.
Everyone is looking at their own benefits. The one who wants to
buy the car, no one cares about it.
He is saying TV, he is saying camera.
See what you want friend. Whatever you like, whatever you get will do.
What can I say,
you have to take the ultimate decision. Guys,
you also tell me in the comments which one you
like,
but we should try a little more,
before buying it, let
us
see a couple more.
Right now I am drinking coffee and
look here, both of them are playing, cool.  Ever since the game
came out, brother, he has liked it so much.  I
play for one hour every day.
Kunal has liked a car.  I just
ordered it.  Guys asks Piyush.   Let us go.
Which car?
Mahindra's.
Which one?
EV.   In which you
can also play games on the
screen.
That's ma'am's million in that.   That
means, there is
a screen of Ma'am's million, in that there is
Ma'am's million.   You
can also play games.  Has something been put into it
or is it there on its own?
Games YouTube Amazon, Netflix
PC wala game hai usne makeup million woh
wali.
That's what he's saying, he's saying,
take that car.  I will go everywhere with you.   It is the
best, it is going well.   It is the
best.
Kunali's TV stopped working.  Hey
Amma, you have become a ghost.
What have you done?  What happened?   Nothing
happened.
So why are you doing this?   The
empty was returning to [sound of clearing throat] beneath it.   Are you
going somewhere to commit some robbery?
Yes, yes I will go to rob.  I have run out of money.
All the money we bought got reduced.  Now I will strike.
Whom will you rob?   I will
go somewhere.   Stay away
from Amma.
Yes Amma, robber.
Amma can come anywhere.   The
bandit will become a bandit.  Otherwise why would she become a
dacoit?
What will you eat Amma?  Please tell.   If you do
n't want, bring some here, I will also eat it.  Whoever
brings it.
Your saree is looking very nice today.
looking good?
Yes.   Are
?   Yes, yes.
looking good.
By the way, you apply red every day, right?
Yes.  Yes,
today you have added green so it looks a little different.
I told you it is thick,
we will
wear it right now.  Thin sarees are good in summer.
We
just cooled down so I took this out.   That
's right Guys.  Well, this is the dream.
Look at this
Usha,
but I don't know when she will come.  After how many years will it
come?  Let's see sometime in the future.
Well, you can buy it to fulfill your hobby
but then you have to look after your future and your family as
well.  There are a lot of things to see.
So when it comes to my mind then I
stop and think that let me see it sometime in the future.
So now I am having
dinner.  Roti and vegetables are ready.  So today I am doing it in the room only.
And today
I have only seen cars etc.  And when you have to take the car home
, there is so much excitement.  That's what goes on
in my mind the whole day.  I keep
watching his videos.  Which one to take?
What to do?  Which brother,
people who like cars can relate this.
So that's what's going on in my mind, friend.  So let's
meet in the next vlog.  Thanks
for watching.  Bye.
[music]